A Guide to the University Union Artist Series, 1959-1980
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University Union Artist Series 1959-1980
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-23/17/2.891
This collection consists of 17 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred on 1989 October 30.
Contents List
- Artists Series 1959-1960 (Box 1)
- Artists Series-Mailing List 1959-1960 (Box 1)
- Artists Series-Philharmonia Hungarica 1959 Oct (Box 1)
- Artists Series 1960-1965, 5 folders (Box 1)
- Artists Series-London Symphony Orchestra 1965-1966 (Box 1)
- Artists Series 1966-1968, 2 folders (Box 2)
- Artists Series-Sesquicentennial 1967-1970 (Box 2)
- Artists Series-Fiddler on the Roof 1968-1969, 2 folders (Box 2)
- Twelfth Night-Oxford Cambridge, Cabell Hall 1968-1970 (Box 3)
- Artists Series 1969-1971, 2 folders (Box 3)
- Fine Arts Festival-Richmond Symphony 1970-1971 (Box 3)
- Artists Series 1971-1972 (Box 3)
- Yevtushenko 1971-1972 (Box 3)
- Artists Series-"Swan Lake" 1972-1973 (Box 3)
- Artists Series 1973-1977, 4 folders (Box 4)
- Artists Series 1977-1979, 2 folders (Box 5)
- Artists Series-Russian State cancels 1979-1980 (Box 5)